It's so dark.
Iiit's soooo daaaark.
Shut it.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Then, can I turn on the lantern?
No.
Awww.
Save it.
We don't know where we'll find
the next refueling station.
Well, we've been in the dark for a while,
so my eyes might've gotten used to it.
We haven't seen the light of day in a while now.
Don't even know how many days it's been.
But seriously, where are we right now?
How'd we get into this place?
C'mon, Yuu, who do you think it was
who said they wanted to go into the hole?
I think it was you, Chi?
It was you.
Come on, that's an old saying, isn't it?
Doesn't it go, "I wish I could just climb into a hole"?
Does it mean it that literally?
In either case, we've gotta find a way out.
We don't have that much food left, huh?
Well, even if we get outta here,
we don't know if we'll find food.
What's gonna happen to us, huh?
When will we get to the top of...
Hey.
Guess I'll sleep, too.
What's the soup like?
It's so smooth...
No, it's so thick...
So warm.
I'm hungry.
I'm cold...
There's a breeze!
Hey, wake up!
C'mon! Yuu!
Yeah. If we go the way the wind's blowing...
...we'll find a way out?
Yeah.
There.
Well?
That way.
Okay.
Now it's that way.
Got it.
Light...
Wow!
It's so bright, Chi!
It was nighttime...
Hey, since we finally made it outside,
let's have some soup, c'mon!
Fine, just to celebrate getting out of there.
Alright, food!
Gotta be good now, right?
Yeah.
Here.
It's our last can.
Right!
Hot!
So good!
I never knew nighttime was this bright.
That's because we were in that
dark cavern that whole time.
It made us sensitive to light.
So what's gonna happen to us when the sun rises?
We'll burn to death.
Shut up!
Hit.
Miss.
Huh?
Alright, last one.
You can keep on going if you want.
Hit.
You wanna shoot, Chi?
No, I'm good.
You're a terrible shot, anyway.
Oh, shut up.
You don't carry a weapon?
I don't need one.
But there are so many.
Most of them are just junk.
But I guess I could go look for one.
It doesn't have to be a weapon.
We might find something we could use.
Maybe we'll find food.
No, if we're looking for food here,
we'll either find something like rations, or find...
Machine gun.
Shells.
Tank.
Hey, you think a tank tastes good?
Give it a try.
Actually try it.
It's like a big weapon graveyard.
People long ago didn't have enough food, either.
So why'd they build all these weapons?
If they'd preserved food instead of making weapons,
our lives would be so much easier.
Well, they had their own problems, you know.
Like war.
Wow! A plane!
Did it really fly?
A long time ago, yeah.
I wanna fly.
That's impossible.
You wanna fly too, right, Chi?
Nope, not at all.
Is this a weapon, too?
I dunno.
But it was probably a bomber or something...
War means killing one another, right?
Why'd they do that?
Dunno. Their interests probably didn't
coincide with... the other side's!
So like, if there are three people,
but only enough food for two...
I bet that's when you've gotta
get your weapon and fight.
Same now, same then...
Huh?
There's a lotta different kinds.
Look, Chi, this looks real powerful!
Put that down.
We don't need guns.
There's something else we could use
way more than that... there!
Explosives.
Yup. We can use them to move stuff
in our way or break down walls.
There's a whole lot.
Yeah.
We'll take as much as we can...
Hey, Chi, what's this?
Dunno.
Rations!
Let's grab them.
Okay!
Ready, up!
Ready, go!
Nope, it's not gonna fly.
We don't need to fly, jeez.
That's too bad.
Not at all.
Look, it can totally fly!
It won't!
We flew!
I'm hungry.
Yeah.
Here's your half.
Thanks.
It's good.
Says it's chocolate flavored.
No idea what chocolate is, though...
There's one more left.
A pack of five? An odd number...
So we'll split it in half and...
Hey!
Don't move.
What are you doing?
I'm taking it.
I see. I should've carried a weapon too, huh...
Yep.
This is war.
Hey! You actually ate it!
Why, you!
Hey, Yuuri!
Ow!
You little, you little!
Ow, ow!
You little brat!
That actually hurts!
That was the last one!
C'mon, Chi!
You little, you little brat!
Chi, jeez!
That was yummy.
J-just you wait.
I moved around too much and now I'm hungry.
The snow's yummy, too.
Having to eat0